I... Howard, focus.
(Penny:)- Tell her what I'm saying.
- Right.
(Howard:)Are you a gold digger or not?
Oh, something, something. Who
the something do you think you are?
(Howard:)Mind your own something business
and go something yourseIf.
Oh, ha, ha, wait, I got this now.
- I'm so mad at you.
- Okay, wait.
How dare you ambush my girIfriend
at the gym?
(Penny:)We didn't mean for it
to be an ambush.
(Penny:)It's kind of impossible not to sneak up
on deaf people.
(Penny:)And, hey,
since when are you so chatty?
- I'm hammered.
- Raj, come here.
(Penny:)This girl is trouble.
(Penny:)What kind of relationship is it where
you buy her gifts and she gives you sex?
The best one l've ever had.
(Penny:)Okay, come on,
you know you can do better.
Aha!
(Raj:)I see what's going on here.
(Raj:)You and I had our crazy night
together.